Welcome to Psyche Awakens, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet.
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle.
Here's how we roll.
House rules, debate ideas, not people.
No doxing, slander, hate or threats, ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumor relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning time out, ban,
no negotiations mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's rules, he keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained. Welcome. If you're here to sow chaos hang out. There's a place for you here, too
Now welcome your host psyche. See ya storyteller and your host e-truth first shadow second
Let's get into it
Hello
Wow, I just see this thing like it looks like it's titled after me. Whatever. What's up Jay dog?
I'm sorry you got you got hit and like, you know, I know that any kind of like voices of dissent they like to hide
I just asked for one-on-one. It's like not like I mean
It's not what our relationship supposed to be like one-on-one like isn't it supposed to be like without like chickens
Squawking in the background. I would think that
It's not like a reasonable request. I thought we were like, you know friends, but she's not brave enough to go one-on-one
But if anyone wants to see it's one-on-one you can go over her chat and say hey do one-on-one with psyche
She why she's so afraid
Why some so manipulative? I'm gonna like you know use a mind control voodoo on her. She's so weak-minded
What's wrong beta? You're scared like obviously I can't get one-on-one for ten minutes on your show
I would go one-on-one with you, like whatever.
You come over here then, you do one-on-one with me.
Like I don't know, it's like you have to have
Christine there, Eldo there, what the fuck?
So stupid, I can't get out of my side of the story
without people slandering and screaming.
Now they're accusing me of being HIV Awakens Tarot.
Like I would even remind people that there was that rumor.
Like what the, like is...
Mean they're just like now. It's just getting so stupid. I can't take it anymore. I
I'll be happy to end this live and go over there and talk, but I need to hear she said come she'll do one-on-one. I
Mean, why can't you do that? Oh, he has to be on mute so we can unmute in two seconds and go. Oh you blah blah blah. Oh
It's so it's stupid, but so stupid
Yeah, and then she's like oh hi J dog, right and I thought she didn't hide anybody in her chat, you know, and it's like whatever
Yeah, there's a lot of people yeah elders up there talking shit
So I'm not gonna go up there with him talking shit and trying to like you know
Get in the middle of it and change the narrative and stuff like that. I'm not trying to change your narrative
Well in st. Karma, I love you in st. Karma. You know what you've been a good friend to me
Oh
Christine yeah, I know she's a snake. Oh, yeah, she's not around me anymore. I've gotten rid of all the snakes
I've gotten rid of all the snakes
Instant karma. I'm sorry. You're not modded. I have unmodded people like a bunch of times and
Then remodeled them and unmodded them. I just want to make sure you're modded just so no one fucks with you, okay?
Okay
Yeah, like Christine's far away. Wow, what a snake. She was what a snake. Oh
Look now. They got good times elder all my fans. Oh traveling gypsy Sam and okay. Everyone's up there now
Everyone's up there now. I can't do I can't do five minutes alone one-on-one without guys seriously
What the hell I
Mean I'm totally willing to talk. I'm like and then she's trying to say oh, I bought oh someone bought
It's just like so dumb. I had a show before I met her
I was well into it. I met through Benny Benny was the one that started promoting me
So a lot of people from IP two and stuff here you go instant karma
Thank you for staying by me. Yeah, Christiane's keep me far away from you know
Yeah, they're gonna make up with you and keep biting when to use me for content, right?
I mean, it's like what I mean, what are they doing now? I mean what now they're all they're talking about me, okay?
I introduced her to a bunch of those people too, but it's okay
Well at least traveling gypsy for sure
Yeah
But they're not making up with me. They're like they just attack me. It's just like it's ridiculous
It's really ridiculous at this point
It's like no, I can't well
I can't even defend myself the last three times I've been on the show
They're on trip kick all the last three times I've been on the show
It's just me with like a really low mic and bronze bird screaming
Christine screaming
Eldo screaming and then beat is hardly saying anything. I can hardly make a point
So I'll forget about her show if she wants to do a one-on-one. She can do it over here. I mean hey money for 20. I
mean, it's like just like
Ridiculous, she's like, oh, I made you or whatever whoever saying they made me whatever
And I didn't use be it as a stepping stone. I liked be to actually I mean, it's like
What do you think I got a tattoo just for like, you know
Just for shits and giggles. It's like at one time I did care about her
But it's getting less and less and she won't even talk to me one-on-one on the phone
And then she's like revealing my messages. Oh, he wrote this to me yesterday
He wrote this to me yesterday and you're you're complaining about me sharing your messages, but you can't even prove
Okay, you can't even prove that plus it wasn't it wasn't anything on my show. It was like, you know, whatever
She's just pissing me off. It's just like, uh
Okay, I'll stay on my lane. Yeah, Christine is a snake for sure. Oh my god
Yeah
Yeah, I mean I like I've cut way down on my drink. I know I did drink a lot at one point
You know and on the show and it's like that was because I had anxiety like no social anxiety and stuff and
You know when I started my show and then I turned into like a party show now
I have maybe one or two at the most of like hard lemonade. That's all I have
So I don't like black out anymore. I don't forget what I said
I'm like, you know, she doesn't remember shit that she says
She's on tape saying this shit and she doesn't remember it. Oh, how why did you accuse me of my ex-husband when you say things like?
They'll never figure it out in like a real ominous tone
Maybe someone will say what the hell happened. I don't know. Maybe it was a joke. He was in a different country
I don't know. I don't I don't really care. You know, it's just like it's getting so old right now. I'm done with it
We keep if you don't want to work things out. That's fine
Let's go. Let's just go our separate ways. I will I won't be bothering your show anymore. I won't ever go there again
You know jeez
I mean, but it is all seems to be like a lot focused on me and complaining about me the grievances the psyche like you know sour
the sour of sour grapes club and what the fuck
Yeah, yeah, she had ally master computer in her chat always. He's the HIV awakens tarot by the way
I mean, it's like obvious
We typed at the exact same time. It's literally and then now they're saying I've sent a kid up there
I mean it's like or I don't do that shit. I don't try to get people's channels in trouble. I
Yeah
It's really sad and it's really sad that
But did I try it low-key? Did I try did I ask?
Did I say, you know, well the last four or five times I tried to get up there?
I was talked over and it's like disparate. She has all these people. I'm not gonna like bring all these people up on the panel with her
I would talk to her like one-on-one and I want to I even said kind of kind of talk to him the phone
We can talk privately
They're like, oh, he's gonna manipulate you. I
I'm not very good at manipulating. I mean, I'm geez, you know, obviously not look at this. Look at the fucking
Look at this shit that goes on about me. I mean, it's like
I have nobody, you know, I do have people on my side and thank you guys for being here. Yeah, I did try I
Asked several times
And then it's like what is it besides being besides cowardice where you can't have any but you can't like talk to me one
Oh, I'll mute them. That's what you said yesterday. Remember what you said yesterday. I'll mute everybody, right?
Nobody was muted
Everyone was talking over me and then bronzer was like, yeah, I'm gonna talk over you motherfucker. So I just left
Yeah, I know a robot streamer. I know
I'm just I'm sick of it
I'm sick of it and talk about like content and it's like I'm not using her for content
She's using me for content at this point, right? And it's like
Nancy I tried I don't understand what's her problem. Why can't she talk one-on-one?
Like five ten minutes. She can't she cast to have this whole panel up because I think it's an important enough thing
She doesn't want to say the relationship obviously, but I was all I've been trying to do
Is like can we just talk without the peanut gallery?
She said she will
Okay
I'll go over there. I'll go over there, but this is my last time. I mean, it's like if she doesn't I
Know I'd love this to happen if she doesn't do the one-on-one you guys are my witnesses
Okay, I'll go over there. I
Want to talk I want to talk without this peanut gallery. Okay
Yeah, what kind of war is this though? I mean it's like I didn't start the war with the fuck
Hold on
And she's disparaging Chona, you know
Chona doesn't buy subscriptions. She like, you know, she has a lot of people in her chat. Yeah, I'll give it a chance
Okay, I'm gonna end this live and I'll go over there. We'll see what happens. Okay
She doesn't control her panels but Christine I noticed that right well Christine stepped out. So maybe we'll maybe I'll have a chance
Okay, I'll go over there
I'll see you over there everyone go over there talk about me not promoting her channel. I'm always promoting her channel
Still I'm promoting her channel. Okay. I'm leaving
I'll see you over there, okay?
They docks, they slander, they gaslight, they disrupt.
But what if you had the ultimate guide to shut them down?
Introducing Trollopedia.
Your field manual to decode, expose, and outsmart internet trolls.
From classic tactics like love bombing to modern swarm attacks, Trollopedia breaks it
all down.
Know the playbook, flip the script, take back your power.
Trollopedia.